欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内
皮特 你要是在等这束阳光
I might be a while if you're waiting
可能还得多等会儿
for the shaft of light, Pete.
没事儿 你慢慢来
Oh, that's okay, you take your time.
看着你开心 我也开心
Gives me pleasure to see you getting pleasure.
算了 让给你
Just take it.
杰在亚马逊买的
Ooh, Jay's new TV arrived
新电视机到啦
from Amazon Prime.
不是昨天才下单吗
Didn't he just order that yesterday?
现代的货物运输可真是令人惊叹啊
The modern transport of goods is truly a marvel.
如此高效 挽救了多少马匹的命
So much efficiency, so few horse deaths.
杰 大家都在 你可以宣布了
Jay, they're here, you can make your announcement now.
好了 是这样的 大家
Okay, here's the deal, people.
这电视仅限活人可看 好吗
This is for Livings only, okay?
我需要一台不被鬼鬼们控制着
I need one TV that isn't dominated
成天播放垃圾真人秀的电视
by ghosts watching trash reality.
《健美运动员的妻子》才不是垃圾呢
Bodybuilder Wives is not trash.
那是七位勇敢女性背后的故事
It's a peek behind the curtain of seven brave women
以及她们爱的肌肉男
and the musclebound men they love.
可是《浪女之战》
Although, Skank Wars...
好吧 这个没什么可抵赖的
Sure, that's harder to defend.
伙计们 杰为建造餐厅
Guys, Jay has been putting in long hours
投入了太长时间
planning the restaurant.
应该让他好好休息 放放轻松
He deserves to relax, kick back,
用4k电视看看尼克斯队输球
watch the Knicks lose in 4K.
太损了吧 宝儿
Good smack talk, babe.
说到餐厅
SASAPPIS: Speaking of the restaurant,
杰有再考虑下我的主意
has Jay given any more thought to my idea
放一台披萨烤箱吗
about putting in a pizza oven?
燃气或柴火都行 我不挑
Gas or wood- fired, I m not picky,
不过还是柴火烤披萨更好些
but, you know, probably wood- fired.
萨斯又在问买披萨烤箱的事了
Sass is asking again about you buying a pizza oven.
抱歉 萨斯亲
Sorry, Sassarino,
只是它跟餐厅的格调不太搭
it just doesn't work with the kitchen layout.
首先 告诉他别再这么叫我
First, tell him to never call me that again,
然后请向他
and then convey
传达我对不买烤箱深切的失望之情
my deep disappointment about the oven.
我们把电视放哪儿 宝儿
JAY: So what are we thinking, babe,
挂在这面墙上吧
hang it on this wall, right?
我说不好 我觉得大家
Oh, I don't know, I think people
通常喜欢把电视挂在壁炉上
usually put them above the fireplace.
这里是目光焦点
Sort of a focal point.
什么 那也太高了
What? That's way too high.
电视应该放在和人坐着时视线齐平的地方
You want the TV to be at eye- level when you're sitting.
这叫最佳视角
It's called optimal viewing angle.
这话说得也太傲慢了
Oof, that was dripping with condescension
就是这种态度才让马真塔
That's the attitude that got Magenta
在《浪女之战》中被踢出局
kicked off of Skank Wars.
说的没错 但如果放在那儿
Right, but if we put it there
那我们的沙发就只能背靠门
then we'd have the back of the couch facing the door,
这就把风水给破坏掉了
and that's bad feng shui.
这事儿上我和杰意见一致
PETE: I got to go with Jay on this one.
我可不想伸长了脖子看电视
You don't want to be craning your neck
本人可是很了解脖子痛是什么感觉的
and that's coming from a guy who knows about neck pain.
加一 詹姆斯·麦迪逊的狩猎版画
Agreed. James Madison's hunting print
就挂的高了几英尺
was hung several feet too high.
蜡烛燃烧的时候
We could barely stare at it
我们都坚持不住一直抬着头看
for the entire burn of a tallow candle.
你们过去还真无聊啊
Wow, you guys did not have a lot to do back then, huh?
我们可是发明了民主啊
Other than invent democracy?
在欧洲人之中
Amongst Europeans.
鬼鬼们喜欢这意大利红酱吗
How are the ghosts liking the marinara?
谈论食物会让索尔想起花花
Talk of food remind Thor of Flower.
她活着的时候也吃食物
She also ate food when alive.
经常吃
Many times.
-他们还挺喜欢  -他还没缓过来呢
They seem to be enjoying it. TREVOR: Well, he's still struggling.
我很同情他 但花花去了更好的地方
I feel for the guy, but she's in a better place.
任何地方都比这里好
Any place would be better than here.
我就是被困在自己老家的囚犯
A prisoner in my ancestral home,
我的厨房里装满了异国的食物
my kitchen reeking of exotic foods.
这是意面
It's spaghetti.
这么多元音
So many vowels.
我理解索尔的沮丧心情
I understand Thor's frustration.
不管怎样 花花也是他第三个升天的情人
After all, Flower was his third paramour to be sucked off.
是吗
She was?
哦对 我总是忘记
Oh, that's right, I keep forgetting.
卢埃拉和弗拉特·玛丽亚升天的时候你们都不在
None of you were around for Luella or Flat Maria.
弗拉特·玛丽亚
Flat Maria?
不亲眼看到
Until you've seen it,
你无法想象一群牛能对人类身体造成多大的伤害
you can't imagine what a herd of cattle can do to the human body.
杰 这也太悲伤了
Oh, Jay, this is so sad.
艾萨克刚刚说
Apparently, Isaac says
索尔交过三个女朋友
Thor's had three girlfriends,
她们在和他约会后
and they all got sucked off
都升天了
after dating him.
可怜的家伙
Aw, poor guy.
感觉就像是
Sounds like he's got a Good Luck Chuck
《好运查克》
situation going on.
《幸运查克》是一部电影 里面的主角叫查克
Good Luck Chuck is a movie about a guy named Chuck
睡过超多女人
who slept with a lot of women.
完美人设
Flawless premise.
每个女火在和他约会之后
And every woman that he hooked up with
都会遇到自己的真命天子
would marry the next man that she met.
如果杰说的没错
So, if Jay is correct,
这的确是《幸运查克》剧情上演
and this is indeed a Good Luck Chuck situation,
难道真的每个
do we believe that any woman
和索尔约会过的女人
Thor becomes romantically entangled with
都能够升天吗
may end up getting sucked off?
有可能
ISAAC: Possibly.
那个可怜的维京人
That poor Viking bastard.
有趣
Interesting.
杰·阿伦德卡尔罚球
ANNOUNCER: Jay Arondekar at the charity stripe,
胜负未分
game on the line,
他要赢得此次比赛
to win the championship
拯救世界
and save the world.
披萨烤箱
Pizza oven.
-什么  -去买一台披萨烤箱
What? Get a pizza oven.
你想要一台披萨烤箱
You want a pizza oven.
没有披萨烤箱就活不下去
You can't live without a pizza oven.
第二发
Shooting two.
太好了
Yes!
柴火烤披萨
Whoo! Wood- fired!
柴火烤披萨 柴火烤披萨
CROWD: Wood- fired! Wood- fired!
柴火烤披萨
Wood- firedl Huh?
CROWD: Wood- fired!
你好呀 索尔
Hey there, Thor.
打扰你了嘛
Am I interrupting anything?
我想着来 鼓励你一小下
I thought maybe you could use some... cheering up.
不打扰 索尔只是在想
Not interrupting. Thor just thinking about emptiness
宇宙的空虚 存在的虚无
of universe, futility of existence,
美味的鳕鱼
deliciousness of cod.
可怜的索尔
Poor Thor.
你经历了太多痛苫
You've been through a lot.
或许我可以
Maybe there's some way I can...
帮你放松下
help you relax.
你真是 太善良了
Oh, yes, that...very kind.
我总是忘记狼尿有多刺鼻
I always forget how pungent that wolf urine is.
那品质是最好的
Is highest quality.
第一次挤爆狼尸体的膀胱
First squeeze of dead wolf bladder.
太令人垂涎了
Mm. Is most coveted.
真是有趣极了
So interesting.
感觉真好
It is nice.
再用力些
Don't be afraid to really get in there.
我觉得我已经
HETTY: I believe I'm in as...
用尽全力了
deep as I'm prepared to go.
问个问题
Question:
你个家伙(Hell)
what the H- E- double- hockey sticks
昨晚在萨曼和杰房间做什么呢
were you doing in Sam and Jay's bedroom last night?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你以为我睡着了 但我没有
You thought I was sleeping, but I wasn't,
因为我有睡眠呼吸中止症
'cause of my sleep apnea,
我以为死后就会好了 但并没有
which I assumed I'd get rid of when I died, but I didn't,
所以我白天也总是疲惫不堪
so I'm always a little tired.
嘿 亲爱的
SAMANTHA: Oh, hey, sweetie.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在标记电视要放的位置
Oh, I'm just marking off where the TV would go,
不管是社交论坛 电脑码奴
if, you know, we put it where Reddit and the Geek Squad
还是常理思维都会赞同的地方
and common sense say it should go.
-那你在干嘛  -我今天要一直跟着萨曼莎
And what are you doing? I'm following Samantha for the day.
周三的惯例活动
It's Wednesday.
杰 那样的话沙发就得放这边
Jay, that would mean the couch goes there,
这太不合理了
which is insane.
我说不好
I don't know,
沙发放那边也挺好啊
the couch over there might look nice.
鬼鬼们在笑你呢
Oh, the ghosts are laughing at you.
我本想把这活动改在周四 但是
I was thinking about switching to Thursdays, but
周三是萨曼莎和凯文调情的日子
Wednesday is the day that Samantha flirts with Kevin,
那个送水的家伙
the water delivery man.
-我才没有  -怎么了
I do not. What?
没有
Nothing.
那是怎么回事
So, what is that?
你在挑披萨烤箱吗
Are you looking up pizza ovens?
是啊 好奇怪
Yeah, it was the strangest thing.
我今早起来 就非常肯定
I woke up this morning absolutely certain
我们该买台披萨烤箱
that we should get a pizza oven
-放进餐厅  -你不是说
for the restaurant. SAMANTHA: I thought you said
烤箱和餐厅格调不符吗
it wouldn't fit with the kitchen layout.
改主意也是常有的事 萨曼
The man's allowed to change his mindj Sam.
我不知道
JAY: I don't know.
我一觉醒来就这样认定了
I just woke up convinced,
所以我就想办法处理格调的事吧
so I'm gonna find a way to make it work.
你是大厨你做主
You're the chef.
看来今天是你的幸运日咯 萨斯
Looks like it's your lucky day, Sass.
是啊 幸运的很
Yeah. Very lucky.
我去上视频瑜伽课了
Well, I have Zoom yoga.
: Well, I have Zoom yoga.
我赌50块 那儿一个印度人都没有
50 bucks says there's not a single Indian person there.
昨天 杰还信誓旦旦的说不想要披萨烤箱
So, yesterday, Jay says he doesn't want a pizza oven.
然后你昨晚对他做了些奇怪的事情
Then you did some weird thing to him while he slept,
他醒来就突然想要烤箱了
and he just woke up wanting one?
是啊 多奇妙的巧合啊
Yeah, pretty cool coincidence, huh?
到底怎么回事 萨斯
What's going on, Sass?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我们是室友啊 我的秘密我都告诉你的
We are roommates. I tell you all my secrets.
你知道我幻想着去洛尼安德森河漂流
You know about my Loni Anderson river rafting fantasy.
-你到底想说什么 皮特  -重点是
What's your point, Pete? The point is, I telt you
我什么都告诉你 可你显然有事瞒着我
everything, and I know there's something you're not telling me.
如果你想着伤害我的杰
And- and if you're doing something to hurt my Jay
你闭嘴吧好吗 声音小点
Would you stop? Keep your voice down, okay?
我不是要伤害杰 听我说
I'm not hurting Jay. Just listen.
这是我的鬼鬼超能力
It's my ghost power.
我可以进入到活人的梦里
Okay? I can subtly influence Livings
潜移默化的影响他们的想法 别告诉别人
by going into their dreams. Just don't tell anyone.
我的老天爷啊 这超能力太强大了
Cheese and crackers. That's incredible.
我滴个老天鹅
Holy guacamole.
别再感叹了 真的很烦人
Would you please stop swearing cleanly? It's very annoying.
只是 这超能力也太强大了 香蕉你个巴拿拿
PETE: It's just, that's one heck of a ghost power. Cookie Crisp.
士多啤犁苹果橙 你可以进入到别人的梦里啊
I mean, dip my chip, you can jump into other people's dreams?
是的 别问了 只有索尔知道
Shh! Yes, okay? And no one knows other than Thor,
我只能告诉他 做那么多年来
who I had to tell because we were alone together
这里只有我们俩 那可是无数尴尬对望的瞬间啊
for many years, and there were a lot of awkward silences.
那你可以操纵别人做事咯
So, you can just make people do whatever you want?
没那么简单 我得获得他们的信任
Well, it's not that simple. I have to gain their trust,
时不时的出现在他们的梦里
repeatedly show up in their dreams,
这人还得意志不那么坚定
and the person has to be susceptible.
还好 杰的思维就像墙头草
Luckily, Jay's mind is like taffy.
那你经常去杰梦里和他玩咯
Wait, so- so you're, like, always hanging out with Jay, huh?
他会梦到些什么
Yeah. What- what does he dream about?
-基本上都是打篮球  -好吧
Uh, mostly basketball...Cool.
-太空旅行  -有趣
and space travel. Love that.
有时候会梦到萨曼
And, sometimes, he has a dream about Sam
-穿着莉亚公主的比基尼  -我就知道
in that, uh, Princess Leia bikini. Of course he does
老婆就是杰的天
Jay's a real wife guy.
但我得说一句
Hmm. But I got to say, I mean,
这感觉不太道德吧 萨斯 这不是意念控制吗
this doesn't seem ethical, Sass. I mean, mind controlling people?
你什么都不许说 皮特
Don't you dare say anything, Pete.
我们是室友 要为彼此保守秘密
Okay? We're roommates, right? We keep each other's secrets.
但这个关系到其他人
But this affects other people.
我觉得萨曼和杰
I mean, I- I don't think Sam and Jay
不会喜欢你的所作所为
would appreciate what you're doing.
但我知道会有谁喜欢
Well, I know someone who would appreciate it.
如果杰把你最爱的露营食物
When Jay puts your favorite camping treat- -
棉花糖夹心饼干 放进餐厅菜单里
s'mores- - on his restaurant menu.
我可以帮你实现
I can make that happen,
只要你配合我
if you play ball.
考虑下吧
Just think about it.
全麦酥饼
Graham cracker,
巧克力 还有中间夹的白白软软的
chocolate, and that white stuff
一百年前出现的美味
that showed up, like, 100 years ago.
-棉花糖  -棉花糖
Marshmallow. Marshmallow.
不 不行
No! I can't.
我唯一想要的夹心
Look, the only s'more I'm interested in
就是你正直的心
is s'more integrity around here.
你这人真没劲
Ugh. You're so lame. Yeah,
或许你说的对 但至少我夜晚能够安眠
that may be true, but at least I can sleep at night.
我是说 如果没有呼吸暂停病的话
Well, I mean, if it weren't for the apnea,
这病死了以后还有可真是太奇怪了
which, again, is so weird that that exists in the afterlife.
你没事吧 特雷弗
Hey. You doing okay, Trevor?
你看上去像是
You look like when Sam and Jay
被萨曼和杰设置了上网时长管控
put parental controls on the Internet.
我觉得我和海蒂或许没办法继续了
I don't think things are working out with me and Hetty.
你俩不是分手了吗
Didn't you two break up?
哦 没有 我们只是这样告诉你们
Oh, right. No, we just told you all that
这样我们偷偷摸摸的偷情更刺激
so we could sneak around, which makes the sex hotter.
你们这俩孩子玩的可真花
Child, you two are exhausting.
我知道
I know.
我刚刚看到她
Anyway, I just saw her
在勾引索尔
trying to seduce Thor.
等等 什么 我们的那个索尔
Wait. What? Our Thor?
不知道代词怎么用的那个索尔
”Never learned pronouns"Thor?
是的 我知道她不是真的看上索尔了
Yes. Although, I know it's not like she's into him for real.
她只是想被吸上天
She's just trying to get sucked off.
等等 给我讲讲怎么回事
Uh- uh. Back up. Walk me through this.
艾萨克告诉我们花花其实是
Okay, Isaac told us that Flower's actually
第三个索尔被吸上天的女朋友了
the third girlfriend of Thor's to get sucked off.
所以大家觉得他就是升天的门票
Basically, people think he s like a ticket to heaven.
有趣
Interesting.
这多恶心啊 不是吗
I mean, it's gross, right?
这样利用他
Using him like that?
更不用说这对我来讲有多侮辱人
Not to mention, completely rude to me.
太有趣了
Very interesting.
皮特告诉我你干了什么 萨斯
SAMANTHA: Pete just told me what you ve been up to, Sass.
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
你一直在进入我丈夫的梦境
You've been entering my husband's dreams
试图操纵他的想法
to manipulate his thoughts?
好吧 是这样 但我真的想要披萨烤箱
Okay, yes, but I really wanted a pizza oven.
等等 艾萨克呢 今天不是他尾随你的日子吗
Wait, where's Isaac? I thought he was shadowing you today?
他在做婴儿式瑜伽动作的时候睡着了 所以我就溜走了
Yeah, he fell asleep during child's pose, so I snuck out.
重点是 这样做严重侵犯了我们之间的隐私和信任
The point is, this is a huge breach of trust and privacy.
吏别说这也太惊悚了 别再进杰的脑子了
Not to mention, it's creepy. Just stay out of Jay's head.
抱歉 知道了
I'm sorry. Lesson learned.
-谢谢你  -知道吗
Thank you. And you know what?
我很为你骄傲 萨曼
I'm proud of you, Sam.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我只是觉得
Well, I just think that
要换作其他的妻子 没你这么大义凛然的
another wife, a lesser wife,
或许会想要让这超能力为她所用
might want to use this power to her own benefit. Like,
比如说 赢得一场胜负击定的夫妻争论
I don't know, to win an ongoing marital dispute.
你们决定好把电视装在哪里了吗
Did you guys ever decide where to put the TV, by the way?
你什么意思
What are you saying?
你知道我什么意思
Oh, I think you know what I'm saying.
你也知道在哪儿能找到我
And you know where to find me.
你在这儿呢
Oh, there you are.
做完瑜伽真是神清气爽
Man, I feel refreshed.
现在该下楼去办公桌整理这周的邮件了
Now, down to the desk for the weekly sorting of the mail.
周三真快乐哟
: Wednesdays.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
特雷弗
Trevor.
你遇到什么烦心事了吗
Is something troubling you?
是 我的确有烦心事
Yeah, something's troubling me.
我们已经是在偷情了
We're secretly hooking up
你还偷偷摸摸的想勾搭我室友
and you're secretly trying to hook up with my roommate.
你是在说索尔吗
Oh, you're talking about the hor thing.
这没什么好偷偷摸摸的
Well, there's nothing secret about it.
我光明正大 连门都没关
I was most overt I left the door open.
我们压根没法儿关门
We literally can't close doors.
好吧 我知道你为什么不开心
Okay, I get why you're upset.
但如果
But if you
你真的在乎我
truly cared for me,
难道不希望我和你的室友在一起
wouldn't you want me to get sucked off
然后愉快的升天吗
by being with your roommate?
从某种角度来讲
Well- - In a way,
难道不是你太自私了吗
isn't it you who's being selfish?
重点是
The point is,
我原谅你了
I forgive you.
不 不
No. No. This?
我们之间的关系 结束了
You and me, is over.
你勾搭索尔是不对的
What you did with Thor was wrong.
告诉你 阿尔伯塔也这样想
And just so you know, Alberta agrees with me.
阿尔伯塔知道索尔的神奇能力了吗
Alberta knows about Thor's magic hammer?
是啊 她还觉得你的行为非常有趣
Yeah, and she found your behavior"very interesting. "
-她是这样说的  -是啊 还说了两次
Is that what she said? Yeah. Twice.
所以
So.
抱歉了 姐们儿 但我离开这道门
sorry, sister, but I'm walking through this door
-就不会回来了  -我走了
and I'm not coming back. I've got to go.
早啊 亲爱的
SAMANTHA: Oh, morning, sweetie
-睡得好吗  -好极了
How'd you sleep? Incredible.
你知道咱家的工具放哪儿了吗
Do you know where our tools are?
我睡得不好
I did not sleep well.
我的舌头整个滑到喉咙里了
My tongue literally slips into my throat.
嗓子眼里的箭已经够占地方了
Which is already pretty packed real estate.
你要工具干什么
Why do you need the tools?
我要去把电视挂起来 我醒来后又想了想
I'm going to hang the TV. I woke up thinking about it
我觉得你说的对
and you know what? You were right.
-什么  -真的吗
What? Really?
对啊 最佳视角有什么好的
Yeah, I mean, who cares about optimal viewing angle?
你想把电视挂在壁炉上
You want the TV over the mantle.
不 这不是你的想法 这是她的想法
No, you don't, that's what she wants.
我真不敢相信
I cannot believe you.
你现在竟然利用萨斯达到你的目的了
Now you're using Sass to get what you want?
杰 这不是什么大不了的事
Well, Jay, it was such a trivial matter.
根本不值得争论
And not remotely worth getting worked up about.
但我很高兴我们达成一致了
But I'm glad it's behind us now.
你是位很坏的女士 坏坏的女士
You're a bad lady. A bad, bad lady.
走进房间看到沙发的背面
I mean, walking in and seeing the back of the couch.
难道我们是动物吗
I mean, w- what are we, animals?
-对吧  -坏女士
Right? Bad lady!
我一直在想你那天
ALBERTA: You know, I was thinking about that story
跟我讲的故事
you were telling the other day.
就是你操着自己雄壮的臂膀
The one about you raiding that village
突袭了那个村庄
using those big, strong arms of yours.
索尔的这种光辉事迹多了去了 能说详细些吗
That's many of Thor's stories. Can you be more specific?
就是你徒手把一头猪撕成碎片的那次
The one where you ripped a pig apart using your bare hands.
你还记得是什么种类的猪吗
Do you remember what type of pig?
索尔 我正要找你呢
Thor? Just the man I was looking for.
阿尔伯塔 我能单独和他聊聊吗
Alberta, mind if I steal him for a sec?
我们正忙着呢
Actually, we're kind of in the middle of something.
我想也是
I bet you are.
不过 我的确得跟索尔单独聊聊
Unfortunately, I really must speak with Thor alone.
你想和索尔说什么 都不用避着我
Whatever you need to say to Thor you can say in front of me.
让开 女人
Back off, woman.
得让我先来 你欠我的
Mm. I go first. You owe me.
你儿子杀了我 你替他隐瞒了一个世纪
Your son killed me and you hid it for a century!
我在这儿被困了一个世纪了
I've been stuck here longer than you.
最应该升天的只能是我
If anyone's getting sucked off, it's gonna be me.
你说什么升天
What do you mean, "sucked off"?
你听错了
You misheard me.
我们来聊聊鳕鱼吧
Let's talk about cod.
多美味的鳕鱼啊 皮薄肉肥
Oh, wonderful fish. Flaky. Mm.
够了
Enough!
告诉索尔到底怎么了
Someone tell Thor what's going on here.
索尔
HETTY: Thor...
我们
we have.
听说
been informed.
你只要跟谁约会
that when you date someone,
她就会被吸上天
they tend to get sucked off.
所以你们
So you just
只是利用索尔到达英灵殿
using Thor to get to Valhalla?
贪婪掠夺索尔
Preying on Thor's
和花花痛苦的过往
painful past with Flower,
还有卢埃拉
Luella,
弗拉特·玛丽亚
Flat Maria.
我的小可心儿
My little pancake.
我需要你用能力提醒杰
So I need you to use your power to alert Jay.
写在镜子上 或者给他发个信息
Write on the mirror, send a text message.
我不想介入这事儿 但需要有人提醒他
I don't want to micromanage, but he needs to be warned.
等等
Hold up.
这么久以来 萨斯一直可以用超能力
This whole time, Sass has had the ability
控制活人的梦
to manipulate Livings' dreams?
是啊 现在萨曼也利用他
Yep. And now Sam is getting him
帮助自己达成邪恶的目的了
to use it for her own evil purposes.
你敢相信吗
I mean, can you believe that?
萨斯可以用自己的能力
So, Sass can use his power
帮助其他人得到他们想要的
to help other people get what they want?
-是啊  -有趣
Exactly. Interesting.
我不觉得这是个好主意
I don't think it's a good idea.
这似乎有点勉强啊
I mean, we're kind of pushing our luck here.
照做 不然我就发邮件给杰 把你的诡计全揭穿
Do it or I'll email Jay and blow up your whole game.
好吧
You got this.
布洛扎克人在跟踪我们
The Blorzaks are tracking us.
-后方盾牌全部充能  -是的 长官
I want rear shields to full. Yes, sir!
这里是太空报告 太空老大
Here's your space report, space boss.
这正是我担心的
It's exactly what Ifeared.
这里也太空了
That is a lot of space.
要用原子鱼雷吗
Shall we engage the atomic torpedoes?
实际上 我觉得我们需要
Actually, what I think we need is
你想要干嘛来着
Oh, what was. that thing you wanted?
一张凯西·爱尔兰的海报
A Kathy Ireland poster.
-她是《体育画报》的泳装模特  -好
She was a Sports Illustrated swimsuit model. Okay.
唯一能够拯救这艘船的
The only thing that can save the ship
是一张凯西·爱尔兰的海报
is a Kathy Ireland poster.
什么
What?
我的数据库显示
According to my database,
她是20世纪末的一名超模
she's a late 20th century supermodel.
你们干嘛呢
What are you guys doing?
你又潜入杰的梦了
Are you going into Jay's dreams again?
皮特 快回去睡觉
Pete, go back to sleep, okay?
我只是在帮特雷弗 没什么的
I'mjust helping Trevor. It's not a big deal.
皮特 特雷弗
Pete? Trevor?
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
该死 梦里的杰起疑心了
Damn it. Dream Jay is suspicious.
你是那个披萨裁判
You're the pizza ref.
还有那个让我把电视
And the old fortune teller who told me
挂在壁炉上的老算命先生
to hang the TV over the fireplace.
长官 布洛扎克的军舰已经
Chef, the Blorzakian warships- -
等会儿再说 弗拉冈
Not now, Flargon.
你是
Are you
你是萨斯吗
Are you Sass?
他现在开始问我是不是萨萨皮斯了
Now he's asking if I'm Sasappis.
我
I mean...
我不是
No, I'm not.
那你怎么知道他的全名叫什么
Then how did you know his full name?
萨曼逼我的
Okay, Sam made me do it.
好吗 萨曼逼我的
Okay? Sam made me do it
我喜欢你原本想挂电视的位置
and- and I like the TV where you wanted it.
我逮到你了
You are so busted.
这是你自己织的网 萨曼
PETE: You made your bed, Sam.
现在作茧自缚了吧
And now you got to lie in it.
明白不
Get it?
因为她正裹着被子睡觉
Because she's sleeping.
还犯下了欺诈的行为
And also guilty of a deceitful act.
嘿 亲爱的 早安呀
JAY: Hey, sweetheart. Good morning.
我做了你最喜欢的煎蛋饼
I made you your favorite frittata.
你真好
That's so sweet of you.
里面什么都没有啊
There's nothing there.
因为我没做煎蛋饼
Because I didn't make you a frittata.
我骗了你
I lied.
自己的伴侣不可信的感觉很糟糕吧
Sucks when you can't trust your partner, right?
杰知道了 他什么都知道了
Jay knows, he knows everything.
我猜到了 萨斯
Yeah, I got that, Sass.
有趣哦 你那个隐形的
Oh, interesting. Is your invisible
诡异梦境潜入者朋友来了
creepy dream creeper here?
告诉他我试着提醒他了
Tell him I tried to warn him.
不好意思 谁能告诉我怎么了
I- I'm sorry, can someone catch me up?
萨斯一直在进入杰的梦
PETE: Sass has been controlling Jay
来控制他 这是他的鬼鬼超能力
by entering his dreams, it's his ghost power.
真的吗 我的能力怎么就是个屁呢
Seriously? And I get the fart thing.
好吧 杰 真抱歉 我这样做太蠢了
Okay, Jay, I'm sorry. It was very dumb of me.
我两天前才刚发现萨斯的鬼鬼超能力的
I only found out about Sass's ghost power two days ago.
我应该立刻告诉你的
I- I should've told you right away.
可你没有 你一心只想赢了我们之间的争端
But no, you wanted to win a stupid argument.
我压根都不在乎电视放哪儿
And I don't even care about the TV.
我在乎的是你辜负了我的信任
I care that you violated my trust.
但我气的不止你一个
But it's not just you I'm mad at.
他没有生我的气吧
He's not mad at me, is he?
我一直都支持他
I had his back all along.
我是因为忠诚才得到的这块奖章
I got this badge for loyalty.
哦不是 这个是摘苹果比赛奖牌
Oh, no, wait, that's apple picking.
我为鬼鬼们做了那么多事
I do so much stuff for the ghosts.
和你不同 我根本都看不到他们
Unlike you, I don't even get to see them.
现在我才知道 一直以来
And now I learn, all this time,
其中一个鬼鬼能够用自己的超能力和我交朋友
one ghost had the power to actually sort of be my friend
可他却把这种超能力
and he took that power
用来控制我为他们做更多的事
and used it to get me to do even more stuff.
萨曼 告诉杰我很抱歉
Sam, just please tell Jay I'm sorry.
萨斯说他很抱歉
Sass says he's sorry.
没事
It's cool.
我知道我在他们心中是什么地位了
I guess I just know where I stand.
我真是松了一口气
Whew. I'm relieved.
索尔
Thor?
我们来向你道歉
We owe you an apology.
我们不应该
It was very wrong of us
试图勾引你达到自己的目的
to try to seduce you for our own benefit.
我们只是太羡慕花花了
The thing is, we were just jealous of Flower.
我和海蒂都有太多
Hetty and I have both had
值得被吸上天的重大时刻
some very big suck off- worthy moments.
不要找借口
There's no excuse.
建立亲密关系是两个
Intimacy is sacred act
相爱的人之间神圣的行为
between two people who love each other.
或是在几十个喝酒狂欢的陌生人之间
Or between dozens of strangers at mead- fueled orgy.
你说的对 我们很抱歉
You're right, we're very sorry that we tried
在这个悲伤的时刻利用你
to take advantage of you at this difficult time.
多谢理解 我的确很悲伤
Thank you. It is difficult.
花花不仅仅是我最勇敢无畏的爱人
Flower not just most adventurous lover,
她还是唯一一个能够花时间
she also only ghost who ever really take time to...
听索尔说话的鬼鬼
listen to Thor.
其实 索尔
You know, Thor,
我很想听听你那个
I'd like to hear the rest of that
把野猪撕成两半的故事后来怎么样了
"splitting the pig in half"story.
我也想听听撕野猪的故事
I also want to hear about splitting the pig.
你们只是安慰我
You're just saying that.
你说的对
Damn right we are.
你得把所有血腥的细节一字不拉的全部告诉我们
Now, you tell us and we're gonna listen to every gory detail.
好吧
Okay, well,
很多人不知道的是 猪的弱点在于脊椎
what a lot of people don't know is pig has weak spot in spine.
只要找到了这个点
And once you locate spot, well,
就能像撕山羊一样把它撕应两半
you can just rip it in half just like goat.
嘿 大块头
Hey, big guy.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
我本想着你会是一个人
I was actually hoping to catch you alone.
他已经知道《幸运查克》那件事了 南希
He's wise to the whole Good Luck Chuckthing, Nancy.
《幸运查克》哪件事
What Good Luck Chuckthing?
我只是满怀敬意的给索尔一个
I was just waiting a respectful amount of time
缅怀花花的时间 但是
post- Flower, but, uh...
咱们摊牌吧
Cards on the table.
我想爬上这棵大树
I want to climb that tree.
从下爬到上
To the top.
阿伦德卡尔再次站到了罚球线后
ANNOUNCER: Arondekar at the free throw line again,
但这次他只是悲伤的坐在地上
but this time he's just sitting sadly on the floor.
多么惊人的逆转啊
What a turn of events.
-嘿 杰  -让我猜猜
Hey, Jay. Let me guess.
又是海蒂想要什么鬼鬼可卡因了吗
Hetty wants a mound of ghost cocaine?
你要是能做到
Uh, I mean, if that's something you could arrange,
她肯定不会拒绝的啦
I'm sure she wouldn't turn it down,
但这不是我来的原因
but that's not why I'm here.
现在裁判和阿伦德卡尔一起坐在了地上
ANNOUNCER: And now the referee is sitting down with Arondekar.
真没想到啊
This is unprecedented.
我想亲囗告诉你 我真的很抱歉 杰
I wanted to tell you myself I'm really sorry, Jay.
我不会再这样操纵你了
I'm never gonna trick you again.
不过也是因为你知道我长什么样子了
Partly because now that you know what I look like,
再这样也不会管用了 但主要是因为
it won't work, but mostly because
我不能这样对待朋友
you don't do that to a friend.
-你想和我交朋友吗  -是啊
You want to be friends? Yeah.
我们在星舰上和布洛扎克打的很开心呢
We had a lot of fun fighting those Blorzaks.
如果你不觉得无聊
And if it's not too boring,
我们隔三差五可以一起玩玩
maybe we could hang out once in a while.
我很乐意
I'd like that.
来抱抱
Bring it in.
他和裁判抱在了一起
ANNOUNCER: He's hugging it out with the ref.
杰的对手惊呆了 其中一个还是
Jay's opponents are stunned. One of whom
他高中的微积分老师
appears to be his high school calculus teacher.
你的作业交了吗 杰
Where's your homework, Jay?
你还好吗
Everything okay?
没事 宝儿 我只是做了个美梦
Yeah, babe, just having a good dream.
《幸运查克》播完了
And that was Good Luck Chuck.
大家看得开心吗 如果你们真的在的话
Hope you all enjoyed, if any of you are actually in here.
查克其实很幸运
Chuck very lucky.
在故事的结局 查克找到了真爱
For in the end, Chuck find love.
不过可悲的是
But, alas.
索尔芬却没有一个幸福的结局
for Thorfinn there will be no happy ending.
怎么了
ISAAC: What's going on?
杰怎么不去书房看新电视
Why isn't Jay watching the new TV in the den?
他们放弃了 这个话题总是争论不休
Ugh, they gave up on that. Too much arguing.
于是他们决定让大家谁都不痛快
They decided it was better that no one be happy.
这就是婚姻啊
Marriage, am I right?
别这样说嘛 艾萨克刚订婚
Hey, please don't say that. Isaac's engaged.
婚姻很美好的 艾萨克
Marriage is great, Isaac.
你妻子可是劈腿了你最好的朋友啊
Your wife was sleeping with your best friend.
我又不知道
But I didn't know that.
你说的对 好有道理 皮特
You're right. Good point, Pete.
杰 我们把这些装饰品都挂上吧
Hey, Jay, what do you say we put these decorations up?
万圣节就要到了
Halloween is just around the corner.
好主意 宝儿
Sounds good, babe.
稍等 万圣节
Wait a minute. Halloween.
还记得去年我们用降神会从天堂把那个
Remember last year we brought that super hot maid
超级性感的女佣召了回来吗
back from heaven with the seance?
你是想说今年万圣节
Are you saying we should bring Flower back
我们把花花召回来
from heaven this Halloween?
就不能过一次正常的万圣节吗
Can we please have one normal year?
太好了 今年的万圣节
Yes! This Halloween,
我们要把我的女朋友从天堂带回来
we bring back my girlfriend from heaven!